{
    "id": "baaf4af299094528b020627a6161599c",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It is worse ………………… I thought.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d00f7f48115b4159849fd27f44a533b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………. young to get married.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6f110639652f476bae72dc7adb8a9a97"
        },
        {
            "question": "China is …………….. India.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bigger than",
                "bigger then",
                "as big"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "830974d416c64a668d35200c9e525758"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is …………………. in the team.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "best",
                "the best",
                "better"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2276961cfafe4488bb28d05f72bac670"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is not as tall ………………….. she is.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "so",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "84e3d6ae0dd44db9b1f8db2ed68edd70"
        },
        {
            "question": "Even a sweeper earns …………………. I do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more then",
                "more than",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "43fa09ad0d93451e809e68e98866c4ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was …………………. girl I have ever seen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "prettiest",
                "the prettiest",
                "the most pretty"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3199c15f731143c59183ab9f7866e856"
        },
        {
            "question": "The day was ………………….. hot that we didn’t go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8fb05ae7fe1b4022a5f6d474a5af93f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "They would like …………………. information about the subject.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "further",
                "farther",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "450309f3b74d483b8fc2be38821e3626"
        },
        {
            "question": "The museum has got ………………….. collection of antique objects.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fine",
                "finest",
                "the finest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "390e6a3432094d959b2fc4d7453f3daf"
        }
    ]
}